Marcel Breuer Papers
Marcel Breuer Papers
- Project Records, 1922-1982 (inclusive); 1940-1980 (bulk); 89 linear feet of manuscript material, 24,618 drawings, 6,160 photographs and slides.
  - WILINSKY APARTMENT, Berlin, Germany (1926) [Interior]
    - Drawings, 22
      - Furgarderobe (Oberg) (Nr. 206A) [Leaf 179] (19 Aug 1929), [Working Drawing ] [German]; 1; (originals) (Oversize 23)
      - Garderobe Ob. Flur (Nr. 206) [Leaf 178] (7 Aug 1929), [Working Drawing ] [German]; 1; (originals) (Oversize 23)
      - Herren Schuhschrank (Nr. 198) [Leaf 169] (31 Jul 1929), [Working Drawing ] [German]; 1; (originals) (Oversize 23)
      - Obergeschoss Grundriss (Nr. 202) [Leaf 173] (1 Aug 1929), [Working Drawing ] [German]; 1; (originals) (Oversize 23)
      - Wohnzimmertisch (Nr. 205) [Leaf 177] (7 Aug 1929), [Working Drawing ] [German]; 1; (originals) (Oversize 23)
      - Küchenschrank (Nr. 188) [Leaf 159] (27 Jul 1929), [Working Drawing ] [German]; 1; (originals) (Map-case 75)
    - Photographs, 1
      - Storage wall unit., finished project, detail; (black and white photographs) 1 (Box 119, Folder 33)
  - WISE HOUSE, Wellfleet, MA (1963) [Residential, Single]
    - Drawings, 5
      - Plan, Elevations, Details (Furniture), [Working Drawings]; 3; (originals) (Tube 709)
      - Transparency/Blueline Drawing Sheet with Plans and Elevations, Lighting Plan, [Working Drawings]; 2; (reproductions) (Tube 709)
    - Project Files
      - Correspondence: Client (1962-1963), Howard Wise (Box 128, Folder 27)
      - Correspondence: Contractor (1962-1963), Ernest Rose (Box 128, Folder 28)
      - Correspondence: Manufacturers (1962-1963) (Box 128, Folder 29)
      - Financial documents I: Invoices (1962-1963) (Box 128, Folder 30)
      - Financial documents II: Certificates of payment (1962-1963) (Box 128, Folder 31)
      - Memoranda (1963) (Box 128, Folder 32)
      - Specification and product literature (1962) (Box 128, Folder 34)
      - Transmittals (1962-1963) (Box 128, Folder 35)
    - Photographs, 5
      - Completed platforms, from letter dated 11October 1963 written by H. Wise, finished project, exterior view; (color photographs) 1 (Box 128, Folder 33)
      - Platforms between house and studio, finished project, exterior view; (black and white photographs) 1 (Box 128, Folder 33)
      - Bedroom desk-dresser unit, drawings, detail; (photocopies) 2 (Box 128, Folder 33)
      - Baffle in kitchen and baffle at niche in studio, drawings, detail; (photocopies) 1 (Box 128, Folder 33)
  - WISE HOUSE, ADDITION, Wellfleet, MA (1972) [Residential, Single]
    - Drawings, 4
      - Plan, Section, Elevations, [Working Drawings]; 4; (originals) (Tube 709)
    - Project Files
      - Financial documents: Invoices (1972) (Box 128, Folder 36)
  - WITALIS HOUSE, King's Point, NY (1951) [Residential, Single]
    - Drawings, 26
      - Project Sketch, [Design Development Drawings]; 1; (originals) (Box 73, Folder 9)
      - Site Sketches/Measurements, [Site Surveys]; 3; (originals) (Tube 631)
      - Property Map and Topographic Survey, [Site Surveys]; 2; (reproductions) (Tube 631)
      - Furniture Details, [Working Drawings]; 1; (originals) (Tube 631)
      - Plot Plan, Topographic Site Plan, [Site Surveys]; 2; (originals) (Tube 631)
      - Draft Framing Plans, draft Details, [Design Development Drawings]; 3; (originals) (Tube 631)
      - Preliminary Elevations, [Design Development Drawings]; 5; (originals) (Tube 631)
      - Presentation Sheet (Elevations/Plans), [Presentation Drawings]; 1; (originals) (Tube 631)
      - Plot Plan, Floor Plans, Elevations, Details, [Working Drawings]; 5; (originals) (Tube 631)
      - Framing Plans, Sections, and Details, [Working Drawings]; 1; (originals) (Tube 631)
      - Electrical Plan and Details (4), [Working Drawings]; 1; (originals) (Tube 631)
      - Plot Plan/Floor Plans, [Working Drawings]; 1; (reproductions) (Tube 631)
    - Project Files
      - Building Permit, Application and Documents for King's Point, Nassau County, NY (Box 73, Folder 1)
      - Contract, Owner-Architect Agreement (27 May 1948) (Box 73, Folder 2)
      - Correspondence: Client (Jun 1948-Jun 1952), Edmond V. Witalis (Box 73, Folder 3)
      - Correspondence: Contractor (1950-51), W.L. Oestreicher Co., Inc. (Box 73, Folder 4)
      - Correspondence: Misc. Contractors and Manufacturers (Box 73, Folder 5)
      - Financial Records I (Jun 1948-Mar 1953), Architectural Invoices (Box 73, Folder 6)
      - Financial Records II, Certificates of Payment (Box 73, Folder 7)
      - Legal Documents (Jan 1952-Jul 1952), Correspondence and documents related to arbitration proceedings (Box 73, Folder 8)
      - Office Records, Miscellaneous notes, memoranda and sketch (Box 73, Folder 9)
      - Specifications/schedules, General Specifications, Short Specs. Heating Specs., Hardware Sched., Lighting Fixture Sched. (Box 73, Folder 10)
      - Transmittals (Box 73, Folder 11)
  - WOHNBEDARF STORES, Zurich/Basel, Switzerland (1932) [Commercial], (Alternate names: Wohnbedarf, Zurich/Wohnbedarf, Basel)
    - Drawings, 13
      - Geschirrschrank Für Wohnbedarf [Leaf 430] (28 Oct 1932), [Working Drawing ] [German]; 1; (originals) (Oversize 5)
      - Glastafel- Aufhängung [Leaf 427], [Working Drawing ] [German]; 1; (originals) (Oversize 5)
      - Ladeneinrichtung der Wohnbedarf AG Zürch IM Hause Talstrasse [Leaf 437], [Working Drawing ] [German]; 1; (originals) (Oversize 5)
      - Ladeneinrichtung der Wohnbedarf AG Zürch IM Hause Talstrasse [Leaf 438], [Working Drawing ] [German]; 1; (originals) (Oversize 5)
      - Längsschnitt 1:50 [Leaf 426] (29 Sep 1932), [Working Drawing ] [German]; 1; (originals) (Oversize 5)
      - Bauliche Änderungen der Liegenschaft (Nr. 1001) [Leaf 434] (1 May 1932), [Working Drawing ] [German]; 1; (originals) (Oversize 10)
      - Ladenfront [Leaf 439], [Working Drawing ] [German]; 1; (originals) (Oversize 10)
      - Laden-Grundriss [Leaf 436], [Working Drawing ] [German]; 1; (originals) (Oversize 10)
      - Ladeneinrichtung der Wohnbedarf AG Zürich IM Hause Talstrasse 15 [Leaf 440], [Working Drawing ] [German]; 1; (originals) (Oversize 25)
      - Ladeneinrichtung Der Wohnbedarf AG Zürich IM Hause Talstrasse 15 [Leaf 441], [Working Drawing ] [German]; 1; (originals) (Oversize 25)
      - Packtisch [Leaf 429] (13 Dec 1932), [Working Drawing ] [German]; 1; (originals) (Map-case 76)
      - Schiebetüre [Leaf 442], [Working Drawing ] [German]; 1; (originals) (Map-case 76)
      - Storefront [Leaf 431], [Working Drawing ] [German]; 1; (originals) (Map-case 76)
    - Published Material
      - [Wohnbedarf, Zurich] Der Konfectionair (Sep 1933), 3 clippingpings; (magazine clippings ) (Oversize 19, Folder 16)
      - Bachelor's quarters, (magazine clippings ) (Oversize 19, Folder 16)
      - Showroom, (magazine clippings ) (Oversize 19, Folder 18)
      - View from staircase Schweizerische Bauzeitung (April 1933), (magazine clippings ) (Oversize 20, Folder 30)
      - Ausstellungs- und Verkaufsraum der Wohnbedarf -A.G. Zürich Schweizerische Bauzeitung (April 1933), (magazine clippings ) (Oversize 20, Folder 35)
      - Store window, (magazine clippings ) (Oversize 20, Folder 35)
      - View from upper gallery, (magazine clippings ) (Oversize 20, Folder 35)
      - Showroom, (magazine clippings ) (Oversize 20, Folder 35)
      - View of entire showroom floor, (magazine clippings ) (Oversize 20, Folder 39)
      - View from upper gallery Schweizerische Bauzeitung (April 1933), (magazine clippings ) (Oversize 20, Folder 39)
      - Elevation Schweizerische Bauzeitung (April 1933), (magazine clippings ) (Oversize 20, Folder 39)
    - Photographs, 7
      - Wohnbedarf, Basel. Storefront., finished project, exterior view; (black and white photographs) 1 (Box 119, Folder 34)
      - Wohbedarf, Zurich. Ground floor., finished project, interior view; (black and white photographs) 1 (Box 119, Folder 34)
      - Wohbedarf, Zurich. Ground floor., finished project, interior view; (black and white photographs) 1 (Box 119, Folder 34)
      - Wohbedarf, Zurich. Ground floor., finished project, interior view; (black and white photographs) 1 (Box 119, Folder 34)
      - Wohbedarf, Zurich. Stair detail., finished project, interior view; (black and white photographs) 1 (Box 119, Folder 34)
      - Wohbedarf, Zurich [?]. Upper level., finished project, interior view; (black and white photographs) 1 (Box 119, Folder 34)
      - Showroom [Slide 740], finished project, interior view; (black and white slides) 1 (Box SL-10)
  - WOLFSON TRAILER HOUSE, Pleasant Valley, NY (1950) [Residential, Single]
    - Drawings, 17
      - Rough sketch., [Design Development Drawings]; 1; (originals) (Box 34, Folder 6)
      - Design Development Drawings, 3; (s) (Tube 604)
      - Design Development Drawings, 2; (s) (Tube 604)
      - Plans, Elevations, Details., [Working Drawings]; 5; (originals) (Tube 604)
      - Framing Plan and Details., [Working Drawings]; 1; (originals) (Tube 604)
      - Mechanical Plan., [Working Drawings]; 1; (originals) (Tube 604)
      - Site/Landscaping. Plot Survey., [Working Drawings]; 1; (reproductions) (Tube 604)
      - Electrical Plans., [Working Drawings]; 2; (reproductions) (Tube 604)
      - Basement Plan., [Working Drawings]; 1; (reproductions) (Tube 604)
    - Project Files
      - Contracts, Contractor-Owner. (Box 34, Folder 1)
      - Correspondence: Client (1949-1956), Sidney Wolfson (Box 34, Folder 2)
      - Correspondence: Misc. Contractors and Suppliers (Box 34, Folder 3)
      - Financial Documents I, Certificates of Payment. (Box 34, Folder 4)
      - Financial Documents II, Invoices for Architectural Services. (Box 34, Folder 5)
      - Office Records, Notes, sketches and misc. documents. (Box 34, Folder 6)
      - Specifications/Schedules, Specifications, Lighting Sched., Hardware Sched. Wiring Diagrams [multiple copies] (Box 34, Folder 7)
      - Transmittals (Box 34, Folder 8)
    - Published Material
      - Symmetrical Cantilevers on Asymmetrical Base. House and Home (Jan 1952), 120-23; (tear sheet) (Box 34, Folder 10)
      - Trailer Annex. Herald Tribune (11 Jan 1952), 1 item; (newspaper clippings) (Box 34, Folder 12)
    - Photographs, 36
      - South View [dups], finished project, exterior view; (black and white photographs) 2 (Box 34, Folder 9)
      - Living Room, finished project, interior view; (black and white photographs) 1 (Box 34, Folder 9)
      - Plans, drawings, plans; (photostat) 1 (Box 34, Folder 9)
      - South View [Slide 30], finished project, exterior view; (black and white slides) 1 (Box SL-10)
      - Porch [Slide 66], finished project, exterior view; (black and white slides) 1 (Box SL-10)
      - Plans [Slide 80], drawings, plan; (black and white slides) 1 (Box SL-10)
      - Connecting Link [Slide 103], finished project, interior view; (black and white slides) 1 (Box SL-10)
      - Living Room [Slide 104], finished project, interior view; (black and white slides) 1 (Box SL-10)
      - Studio [Slide 105], finished project, interior view; (black and white slides) 1 (Box SL-10)
      - West Elevation [Slide 106], finished project, exterior view; (black and white slides) 1 (Box SL-10)
      - South View [Roll 10, Frame 1], finished project, exterior view; (negatives) 1 (Box SL-14)
      - South View [Roll 10, Frame 2], finished project, exterior view; (negatives) 1 (Box SL-14)
      - South View [Roll 10, Frame 3], finished project, exterior view; (negatives) 1 (Box SL-14)
      - Porch Detail [Roll 10, Frame 4], finished project, exterior view; (negatives) 1 (Box SL-14)
      - Porch Detail [Roll 10, Frame 5], finished project, exterior view; (negatives) 1 (Box SL-14)
      - West Elevation [Roll 10, Frame 6], finished project, exterior view; (negatives) 1 (Box SL-14)
      - West Elevation [Roll 10, Frame 7], finished project, exterior view; (negatives) 1 (Box SL-14)
      - West Elevation [Roll 10, Frame 8], finished project, exterior view; (negatives) 1 (Box SL-14)
      - Partial West Elevation [Roll 10, Frame 9], finished project, exterior view; (negatives) 1 (Box SL-14)
      - View of Trailer [Roll 10, Frame 10], finished project, exterior view; (negatives) 1 (Box SL-14)
      - West Elevation at Corner of Main House [Roll 10, Frame 11], finished project, exterior view; (negatives) 1 (Box SL-14)
      - View from the South West [Roll 10, Frame 12], finished project, exterior view; (negatives) 1 (Box SL-14)
      - South View [Roll 10, Frame 13], finished project, exterior view; (negatives) 1 (Box SL-14)
      - South View [Roll 10, Frame 14], finished project, exterior view; (negatives) 1 (Box SL-14)
      - View from the South East [Roll 10, Frame 15], finished project, exterior view; (negatives) 1 (Box SL-14)
      - View from the South East [Roll 10, Frame 16], finished project, exterior view; (negatives) 1 (Box SL-14)
      - East Elevation [Roll 10, Frame 17], finished project, exterior view; (negatives) 1 (Box SL-14)
      - East Elevation [Roll 10, Frame 18], finished project, exterior view; (negatives) 1 (Box SL-14)
      - East Elevation at Corner [Roll 10, Frame 19], finished project, exterior view; (negatives) 1 (Box SL-14)
      - Detail of Porch Support [Roll 10, Frame 20], finished project, exterior view; (negatives) 1 (Box SL-14)
      - Detail of Porch Support [Roll 10, Frame 21], finished project, exterior view; (negatives) 1 (Box SL-14)
      - Trailer Detail [Roll 10, Frame 22], finished project, exterior view; (negatives) 1 (Box SL-14)
      - Detail of Porch Support [Roll 10, Frame 23], finished project, exterior view; (negatives) 1 (Box SL-14)
      - View of House in Context [Roll 10, Frame 24], finished project, exterior view; (negatives) 1 (Box SL-14)
      - View of House in Context [Roll 10, Frame 25], finished project, exterior view; (negatives) 1 (Box SL-14)
  - YALE UNIVERSITY, BECTON ENGINEERING AND APPLIED SCIENCE CENTER, New Haven, CT (1967-1970) [Educational]
    - Drawings, 303
      - Perspective rendering (Artist Unknown, n.d.)[graphite, pen and ink on illustration board, 14.25 x 20 in.], [Presentation Drawings]; 1; (originals) (Map-case 112, Folder 6)
      - Perspective rendering - view from across campus (Artist Unknown, n.d.) [graphite, pen and ink on illustration board, 14.25 x 20 in.], [Presentation Drawings]; 1; (originals) (Map-case 112, Folder 3)
      - Interior detail rendering - elevator car (Tyler Company, Design 48513-R) [graphite and ink with montage, 15 x 20 in.], [Presentation Drawings]; 1; (originals) (Map-case 112, Folder 2)
      - Perspective rendering - view from across campus (Artist Unknown, n.d.) [graphite, pen and ink on illustration board, 14.25 x 20 in.], [Presentation Drawings]; 1; (reproductions) (Map-case 112, Folder 4)
      - Perspective rendering (Artist Unknown, n.d.) [graphite, pen and ink on illustration board, 14.25 x 20 in.], [Presentation Drawings]; 1; (reproductions) (Map-case 112, Folder 5)
      - Presentation Set (Sheet Nos. 1-6) [Jun 1965] (includes set master, duplicate print sheets and revised sheet 3R): Site Plan, Floor Plans, Sections, Elevations, [Presentation Drawings]; 11; (originals) (Tube 290)
      - Assignment Plan [n.d.], [Presentation Drawings]; 6; (originals) (Tube 290)
      - Perspective From Corner of Prospect and Grove [29 Jun 1965] (original and print), [Presentation Drawings]; 2; (mixed) (Tube 290)
      - Construction Set [30 Mar 1967]: Title Sheet, Site Plan (AS), Architectural (A1-A46 incomplete), [Working Drawings]; 41; (originals) (Tube 1310)
      - Misc. Details (SUA1) [27 Nov 1967], [Working Drawings]; 1; (originals) (Tube 1310)
      - Construction Set [29 Mar 1967]: Structural (S1-S19 incomplete, and misc. duplicates), [Working Drawings]; 23; (reproductions) (Tube 1311)
      - Plaza Plan: Sidewalk Elevation (A1) [20 Sep 1967] (print with graphite additions), [Working Drawings]; 1; (reproductions) (Tube 1311)
      - Laboratory Changes [20 May 1968] ("issued for cost estimate") (prints with graphite annotations: A2,A5-A7, A38, A40), [Working Drawings]; 6; (reproductions) (Tube 1311)
      - Occupancy and Egress [22 Apr 1966] (prints with graphite additions): A2,A3,A4,A6,A9), [Working Drawings]; 5; (reproductions) (Tube 1311)
      - Laboratory Equipment and Services [Nov 1968] ("NSF") (prints with graphite additions): AS, A2-A9, [Working Drawings]; 9; (reproductions) (Tube 1311)
      - Design Development Drawings (SK1-SK82 incomplete and unnumbered drawings) [Aug 1965-Dec 1966]: includes structural studies, interior elevations, preliminary plans and plan studies, mechanical systems, library plans, auditorium plans, stair sections, building sections, service rack and lighting system for lab, expansion joint details, stair tower studies, lab details, [Design Development Drawings]; 59; (originals) (Tube 1312)
      - Diagrammatic Plan [26 Oct 1964], [Presentation Drawings]; 1; (originals) (Tube 1313)
      - Original Program Scheme (Sheet Nos. 1-13) [1 Sep 1964]: Diagrammatic Plan, Floor Plans, Sections, Elevations, [Presentation Drawings]; 13; (originals) (Tube 1313)
      - Preliminary [27 May 1964]: Site Plans, Floor Plans, Typical Floor Diagram and Occupancy Diagram, [Presentation Drawings]; 5; (originals) (Tube 1313)
      - Preliminary Plan (Dwg. Nos. P6-P9) [Aug-Oct 1965), [Design Development Drawings]; 4; (originals) (Tube 1313)
      - Design Development Drawings [Jul 1965]: includes elevation studies, façade studies, precast panel studies, fire tower plan and elevation studies, building sections, [Design Development Drawings]; 17; (originals) (Tube 1313)
      - Preliminary Drawings (SK2-SK6) (annotated prints) [26 Jan 1966], [Design Development Drawings]; 5; (reproductions) (Tube 1424)
      - Progress Prints (annotated prints) [8 Mar 1966], [Design Development Drawings]; 5; (reproductions) (Tube 1424)
      - Progress Prints (annotated prints) [15 Mar 1966], [Design Development Drawings]; 5; (reproductions) (Tube 1424)
      - Misc. sketches and drawings [n.d.]: includes library interiors and furnishings, [Design Development Drawings]; 17; (originals) (Tube 1424)
      - Construction Sketches (SK-CA1 to SK-CA57 incomplete): includes sidewalk elevations, signage, window and door details, revised framing details, Reflected ceiling plans, [Working Drawings]; 61; (mixed) (Tube 1425)
      - Site Map [May 1958] ("copy of map handed to contractor at Yale meeting 13 April"), [Site Surveys]; 1; (reproductions) (Tube 1425)
    - Project Files
    - Published Material
    - Photographs, 158
      - Progress photos, sets 1 to 16 (1967-1968), construction, exterior view; (black and white photographs) 67 (Box 130, Folder 12)
      - Progress photos, sets 17 to 31 (1969-1970), construction, exterior view; (black and white photographs) 60 (Box 130, Folder 13)
      - Ground Floor Plan, drawings, plan; (black and white photographs) 1 (Box 130, Folder 14)
      - Elevations and façade details (1969-1970), finished project, exterior view; (black and white photographs) 7 (Box 130, Folder 14)
      - Elevations and façade details (1969-1970), finished project, exterior view; (color photographs) 3 (Box 130, Folder 14)
  - YANKEE PORTABLES (1942) (not built) [Residential, Single], (Alternate names: De-mountable Housing)
    Holdings include a full set of Yankee Portables assembly drawings, including assembly schedule and sliding window detail. Plans cover 1, 2, and 3 bedroom units (R-1, R-2 and R-3) and alternate 2 bedroom unit (T-2). Note, as per drawings, R2 details are typical for all types.
    - Drawings, 12
      - Assembly Schedule and Schedule of Drawings., [Working Drawings]; 1; (originals) (Tube 575)
      - T-2 Plans, Elevations and Perspective, [Working Drawings]; 1; (originals) (Tube 575)
      - R-1, R-2 and R-3 Plans and Perspective, [Working Drawings]; 1; (originals) (Tube 575)
      - R-2 Plans and Elevations. Porch Stair Detail. (includes foundation plan), [Working Drawings]; 1; (originals) (Tube 575)
      - R-2 Detail: Vertical Section of Bearing Wall., [Working Drawings]; 1; (originals) (Tube 575)
      - R-2 Detail: Vertical Section of Non-Bearing Wall., [Working Drawings]; 1; (originals) (Tube 575)
      - R-2 Detail: Horizontal Section of Exterior Wall., [Working Drawings]; 1; (originals) (Tube 575)
      - R-2 Panels: Floor and Roof., [Working Drawings]; 1; (originals) (Tube 575)
      - R-2 Exterior Wall Panels: Elevations and Reference Plan., [Working Drawings]; 1; (originals) (Tube 575)
      - R-2 Partitions: Elevations., [Working Drawings]; 1; (originals) (Tube 575)
      - R-1, R-2, R-3 and T-2 Electrical Layouts., [Working Drawings]; 1; (originals) (Tube 575)
      - Sliding Window Details (full-size)., [Working Drawings]; 1; (originals) (Tube 575)
    - Project Files
      - Correspondence, includes notes for manufacturing agreement with Jay Roy Lewis (Box 85, Folder 11)
      - Cost Estimates and Proposal (Custance Brothers) (Mar 1942), proposal as submitted to NHA (Box 85, Folder 12)
      - Office Records, includes sheet of potential names for project (Box 85, Folder 13)
      - Program Notes (Dec 1942), description of project with cost estimates, sent to Jack Pritchard (Box 85, Folder 14)
      - Schedules, Assembly Schedule (Box 85, Folder 15)
      - Specifications, Government Issued: "Defense Housing" and "Demountable Housing" (Box 85, Folder 16)
  - ZUP DE BAYONNE, Bayonne, France (1965-1974) [Urban Planning], (Alternate names: Bayonne)
    - Drawings, 3
      - Town Center - Perspective rendering (Lutz, n.d.) [graphite, pen and ink on illustration board, 11.5 x 21.75 in.], [Presentation Drawings]; 1; (originals) (Map-case 118, Folder 1)
      - Facsimile of: Town Center - Perspective rendering (Lutz, n.d.), [Presentation Drawings]; 1; (reproductions) (Map-case 118, Folder 2)
      - Aerial Perspective (Lutz, n.d.) [graphite on trace mounted on corrugated cardboard, 23.5 x 29 in], [Presentation Drawings]; 1; (originals) (Map-case 118, Folder 3)
    - Project Files
      - Correspondence (1965-1974) (Box 130, Folder 15)
    - Published Material
    - Photographs, 31
      - Ground breaking and progress, construction, exterior view; (color photographs) 8 (Box 130, Folder 16)
      - Construction progess (1966-1967), construction, exterior view; (black and white photographs) 20 (Box 130, Folder 16)
      - Contact sheets, construction, exterior view; (black and white photographs) 3 (Box 130, Folder 16)